Kyle Rassweiler

Phone: 1-613-724-9141 Email: jobs@kylerassweiler.ca

Portfolio: https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca Github: www.github.com/rassweiler

Summary

Engineering specialist with experience in both software and hardware development with schooling focused on embedded development and robtics.

Skills

Angular, Assembly(PIC), C++, CMake, Django, Git, HTML, JavaScript, Software

Mongoose, Node, PHP, Python, React, Redux, Typescript, VBA

Docker, Qemu/KVM, XCP-NG **Virtualisation**

Arch, Debian, FreeBSD/OpenBSD, Proxmox, Windows **Systems**

MongoDB, MySQL, Postgresql, SQLite **Databases**

Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Zigbee Hardware

Projects

A Hatchways assesment for React front-end work. The project React Pagination

required the addition of a pagination system for a sample blog

(Javascript, CSS, HTML, Node,

React)

Krello

Source: https://github.com/kylerassweiler/165b69

A FreeCodeCamp project that generates random tweetable quotes Random Quote Machine

using React.

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

React, Bootstrap)

Website: https://codepen.io/kylerassweiler/pen/rNdJzY0

A FreeCodeCamp project that will preview markdown input into a Markdown Preview

seperate editor window.

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

React, Bootstrap)

(Javascript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

React, Redux)

Kawasaki AS Parser

Website: https://codepen.io/kylerassweiler/pen/LYdQmMz

A simple Trello clone developed using react and redux with jest and enzyme for testing. Used Javascript, SCSS, and HTML to style

the react components.

Website:

https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/posts/software/node/krello/

Demo: https://krello.kylerassweiler.com/

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/krello

A Kawasaki robot backup parser library written in TypeScript.

(Typescript, SCSS, HTML, Node,

Electron)

Website:

https://portfolio.kylerassweiler.ca/posts/software/node/kawasaki-

Source: https://github.com/rassweiler/kawasaki-as-parser

Certificates

Free Code Camp Jav

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

July 2022

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/kylerassweiler/

javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

Free Code Camp

Responsive Web Design

June 2022

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/kylerassweiler/

responsive-web-design

Experience

(VBA, Powerbi, Electron).

Engineering Specialist

PLC programming, Robotic Vision (Robeye system), 3D Factory Design, Robot programming, Project Management, Tools Programming

2017 - Present

TEMA (Toyota)

Robotics Technician

PLC programming, Robot programming, SCADA programing.

2014 - 2017

FIO Automotive

Operational Technician

PLC programming, Robot programming.

2012 - 2014

Abbott Point Of Care

Education

Electro-Mechanical Engineering

Technician

Embedded development, plc programming, circuit and pcb design, motor controls, industrial robotics, microcontrollers.

Algonquin College

Computer Animation

Traditional animation, 3d animation, riging, modelling, python

scripting, layout.

Algonquin College